<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8" standalone="no"?>
<!-- Sid Meier's Civilization 4 -->
<!-- Copyright Firaxis Games 2005 -->
<!-- -->
<!-- Game Text - Events -->
<Civ4GameText xmlns="http://www.firaxis.com">
<!-- MORE EVENTS MOD STARTS lfgr: changed -->
	<TEXT><!-- ERROR_NO_AVAILABLE_EVENT -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_ERROR_NO_AVAILABLE_EVENT</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_RED]This Event is buggy. Please report this bug at https://forums.civfanatics.com/threads/extramodmod-unofficial.646778/ or the thread you downloaded this mod, including the mod version you are playing and the event's name: %s1_event. Thank you.[NEWLINE]In case you're concerned, it is save to play on now.[COLOR_REVERT][NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</English>
		<German>[COLOR_RED]Dieses Ereignis ist fehlerhaft. Bitte melden Sie diesen Fehler unter https://forums.civfanatics.com/threads/extramodmod-unofficial.646778/ oder in dem Forenthread, in dem Sie diese Mod heruntergeladen haben. Nennen Sie dabei bitte die Version der Mod, die Sie spielen, sowie den folgenden Namen des Ereignisses: %s1_event. Vielen Dank.[NEWLINE]Sie können ohne Probleme weiterspielen.[COLOR_REVERT][NEWLINE][NEWLINE]</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_NO_BONUS_UNIT_AVAILABLE -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_NO_BONUS_UNIT_AVAILABLE</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_RED]No appropriate unit type available.[COLOR_REVERT]</English>
		<German>[ICON_BULLET][COLOR_RED]Kein passender Einheitentyp verf&#252;gbar[COLOR_REVERT]</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- NEWLINE -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_NEWLINE</Tag>
		<English>[NEWLINE]</English>
	</TEXT>
	
	<!-- BUG Options for events enhanced -->
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUG_OPT_EVENTSENHANCED__HIDEUNAVAILABLEOPTIONS_TEXT</Tag>
		<English>Hide Unavailable Event Options</English>
		<German>Nicht wählbare Ereignisoptionen verbergen</German>
		<Spanish>Oculta opciones de eventos no disponible</Spanish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUG_OPT_EVENTSENHANCED__HIDEUNAVAILABLEOPTIONS_HOVER</Tag>
		<English>When checked, unavailable event options are hidden.</English>
		<Spanish>Cuando se activa, oculta opciones de eventos que no se puede seleccionar.</Spanish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUG_OPT_EVENTSENHANCED__WUPOPUPHUMAN_TEXT</Tag>
		<English>Enable Human's WU Popups</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUG_OPT_EVENTSENHANCED__WUPOPUPHUMAN_HOVER</Tag>
		<English>When checked, a popup is displayed every time a human player builds a world unit.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUG_OPT_EVENTSENHANCED__WUPOPUPAI_TEXT</Tag>
		<English>Enable AI's WU Popups</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUG_OPT_EVENTSENHANCED__WUPOPUPAI_HOVER</Tag>
		<English>When checked, a popup is displayed every time an AI player builds a world unit.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUG_OPT_EVENTSENHANCED__GPPOPUPHUMAN_TEXT</Tag>
		<English>Enable Human's GP Popups</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUG_OPT_EVENTSENHANCED__GPPOPUPHUMAN_HOVER</Tag>
		<English>When checked, a popup is displayed every time a human player creates a great person.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUG_OPT_EVENTSENHANCED__GPPOPUPAI_TEXT</Tag>
		<English>Enable AI's GP Popups</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_BUG_OPT_EVENTSENHANCED__GPPOPUPAI_HOVER</Tag>
		<English>When checked, a popup is displayed every time an AI player creates a great person.</English>
	</TEXT>
	
	<!-- GELA -->
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GELA -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GELA</Tag>
		<English>The demon Hyborem has been vanquished, and his soul sent screaming back into the pits of Hell. His weapon, the unholy Gela, is all that remains of the mighty demon. Your forces, victorious, reach to claim the weapon that has been left behind. But it is up to you to decide what will become of this demonic legacy.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GELA1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GELA1</Tag>
		<English>I shall keep the weapon. It's strength shall become my own.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GELA2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GELA2</Tag>
		<English>The demonic taint must be washed from this trident. I shall cleanse it in the waters of the Pool of Tears.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GELA3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GELA3</Tag>
		<English>The Gela must be disposed of quickly. I shall hurl it into the great Maelstrom, banishing it to the ocean floor.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GELA4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GELA4</Tag>
		<English>Only the angels of Basium will know how to handle this. I shall entrust the Gela to their care and bring it to their Gate.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GELA5 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GELA5</Tag>
		<English>The Gela must be destroyed! I shall hurl it into the fires of Pyre of the Seraphic.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GELA6 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GELA6</Tag>
		<English>The Gela contains much demonic power. Perhaps I can harness it using the necromantic texts found in the Broken Sepulcher.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GELA7 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GELA7</Tag>
		<English>Perhaps the Gela can be used for good, if properly energized. I shall let it soak up the holy power of the Sun at the Mirror of Heaven. But it will take time.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- MESSAGE_MAELSTROM_GELA_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_MESSAGE_MAELSTROM_GELA_1</Tag>
		<English>The Maelstrom consumes the trident quickly and, miraculously, the waves grow calm. A moment passes as the swirling vortex begins again. Out of the center walks a man with bowed head, wearing the robes of a priest. He is accompanied by four attendants. The Overlords must be pleased.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- MESSAGE_MAELSTROM_GELA_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_MESSAGE_MAELSTROM_GELA_2</Tag>
		<English>The ship is sacrificed and sucked into the turbulent vortex of the whirlpool. A moment passes, and then the seas turn red. A storm begins brewing on the horizon. Something is not right.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EQUIPMENT_PIKE_OF_TEARS -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EQUIPMENT_PIKE_OF_TEARS</Tag>
		<English>Pike of Tears</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- MESSAGE_TEARS_GELA -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_MESSAGE_TEARS_GELA</Tag>
		<English>The Gela is plunged into the cold waters of the Pool of Tears. The demonic taint washes off from the weapon in waves of oily blackness, mixing with the spring. The Gela is no more, and in its place an even more powerful weapon has been created. But at what cost?</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- MESSAGE_TEARS_GELA_PLAGUE -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_MESSAGE_TEARS_GELA_PLAGUE</Tag>
		<English>The demon tainted water is carried far and wide throughout the land. The world suffers, as do the people of Erebus.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- MESSAGE_BASIUM_GELA -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_MESSAGE_BASIUM_GELA</Tag>
		<English>Standing before the holy Gate of the Mercurians, the mighty Basium looks down upon you. You offer up the Gela, and the angel's massive hand reaches down to take it. "You have done well to rid Erebus of the demon Hyborem. The angels shall sing your name in praise. But there is still much corruption in this land. Take one of my finest newly reborn warriors to aid you in your battle."</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- MESSAGE_TEARS_GELA_PYRE_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_MESSAGE_TEARS_GELA_PYRE_1</Tag>
		<English>The Gela is hurled into the flames, which seem to flicker and burn eagerly for the demonic object. The fires die down for a moment before flaring into an intensity that scorches the ceiling of the great temple. Then, miraculously, the flames stop moving and grow black. A piercing cry fills the Pyre, and looking into the flame one can now see the tortured souls used to forge the trident wailing in despair.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- MESSAGE_TEARS_GELA_PYRE_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_MESSAGE_TEARS_GELA_PYRE_2</Tag>
		<English>The Gela is hurled into the flames, which seem to flicker and burn eagerly for the demonic object. The weapon hisses for a brief moment and then, for the first time since it was lit, the fires burn out. The very earth screams out in protest at the magical energies unleashed by the destruction of Gela. The ley lines leading to the Pyre, once invisible to the naked eye, are suddenly illuminated by the energy surging through them. The phenomenon fades, and the temple now lies in ruins.</English>
		<German>The Gela is hurled into the flames, which seem to flicker and burn eagerly for the demonic object. The weapon hisses for a brief moment and then, for the first time since it was lit, the fires burn out. The very earth screams out in protest at the magical energies unleashed the destruction of Gela. The ley lines leading to the Pyre, once invisible to the naked eye, are suddenly illuminated by the energy surging through them. The phenomenon fades, and the temple now lies in ruins.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EQUIPMENT_FROZEN_FLAME -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EQUIPMENT_FROZEN_FLAME</Tag>
		<English>Frozen Flame</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- SPELL_TAKE_FROZEN_FLAME -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_SPELL_TAKE_FROZEN_FLAME</Tag>
		<English>Take Frozen Flame</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- SPELL_DROP_FROZEN_FLAME -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_SPELL_DROP_FROZEN_FLAME</Tag>
		<English>Drop Frozen Flame</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- MESSAGE_GELA_BROKEN -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_MESSAGE_GELA_BROKEN</Tag>
		<English>Using the necromantic texts found in the libraries left behind by Barbatos, you learn how to twist the demonic powers of the Gela to your will. This ritual will unravel the unholy markings of the weapon, allowing you to guide the spirits of the recently departed away from Hell and into your own kingdom. It requires thousands of sacrifices. You are fairly certain you have enough willing subjects.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- MESSAGE_GELA_MIRROR -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_MESSAGE_GELA_MIRROR</Tag>
		<English>Your people place the Gela in the center of the Mirror of Heaven. Inky black smoke begins to rise from the weapon in plumes as the sun purifies it. After a while, the weapon ceases to smoke, and the light of the Mirror shines brilliantly off of its surface. The taint is removed, and in its place a holy trident of great power remains.  This has surely attracted the attention of any demons nearby but your unit needs some time to control the power of the trident.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- SPELL_TAKE_SOL -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_SPELL_TAKE_SOL</Tag>
		<English>Take Sol</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EQUIPMENT_SOL -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EQUIPMENT_SOL</Tag>
		<English>Sol</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_STRANGE_ADEPT -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_STRANGE_ADEPT</Tag>
		<English>A strange adept has recently joined the mage guild of %s2_city. While the student is incredibly smart and talented, all the other students and even some of the instructors steer clear of him. Many claim he delves deeply in necromancy and dark arts, some have observed strange experiments, and everyone says that anyone who gets in his way often falls victim to some strange circumstance.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<!-- EVENT_STRANGE_ADEPT -->
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_STRANGE_ADEPT_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_STRANGE_ADEPT_1</Tag>
		<English>Disturbing, but let the instructors handle it how they will.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_STRANGE_ADEPT_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_STRANGE_ADEPT_2</Tag>
		<English>We need all the proficient Adepts we can get our hands on, let him serve the nation.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_STRANGE_ADEPT_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_STRANGE_ADEPT_3</Tag>
		<English>You tell me this as if it's a problem. Have him advanced immediately.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_STRANGE_ADEPT_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_STRANGE_ADEPT_4</Tag>
		<English>Dark arts? Expel him from our country, he is not welcome here!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<!-- EVENT_HELL_REFUGEES -->
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HELL_REFUGEES -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HELL_REFUGEES</Tag>
		<English>A band of haggard refugees has shown up outside %s2_city. The leader of the group says that they had stumbled upon the true nature of the Ashen Veil religion, much to the chagrin of the higher-ups in their nation. Not wanting to live in Hell, assist it in any way, or become the next demonic sacrifice for what they know, they had no choice but to flee. They seek refuge in a land where they can live free of Hell's taint, and if possible, fight back.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HELL_REFUGEES_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HELL_REFUGEES_1</Tag>
		<English>If they come from an Ashen Veil civilization, they already have Hell's taint upon them. Close our borders to them.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HELL_REFUGEES_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HELL_REFUGEES_2</Tag>
		<English>Any enemy of evil is a friend of ours. Welcome them with open arms and set up housing.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HELL_REFUGEES_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HELL_REFUGEES_3</Tag>
		<English>If they can escape an Ashen Veil nation, they must be very blessed and hardy! Have them enlist in our army.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HELL_REFUGEES_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HELL_REFUGEES_4</Tag>
		<English>Hell's reach is strong, and they know the worst of it. Give their leadership a high religious position, that they may spread their words of truth and give needed advice.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HELL_REFUGEES_5 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HELL_REFUGEES_5</Tag>
		<English>We do not need the eyes of Hell upon us. Sell them back to their Ashen Veil masters at the highest price so that we may avoid confrontation.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HELL_REFUGEES_5_HELP -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HELL_REFUGEES_5_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET]Ceasefire with all Veil Civilizations</English>
		<German>[ICON_BULLET]Waffenstaillstand mit allen Zivilisationen des Aschfahlen Schleiers</German>
	</TEXT>
	<!-- EVENT_SCHOLARS -->
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_SCHOLARS -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SCHOLARS</Tag>
		<English>There has been a recent surge of promising young scholars wishing to study science, magic, and the arcane. %s2_city's current facilities will be overcrowded with activity and suffer material shortages. Additional funding will be needed to expand and accommodate everyone.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_SCHOLARS_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SCHOLARS_1</Tag>
		<English>We cannot afford it.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_SCHOLARS_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SCHOLARS_2</Tag>
		<English>Scholarly study is the foundation of advancement! Expand our libraries.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_SCHOLARS_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SCHOLARS_3</Tag>
		<English>Sounds like good news. Build them a Mage Guild.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_SCHOLARS_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SCHOLARS_4</Tag>
		<English>Scholarly societies are for the weak. Press these foolish youths into our army.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<!-- EVENT_TRAPPED_FROSTLINGS -->
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TRAPPED_FROSTLINGS -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TRAPPED_FROSTLINGS</Tag>
		<English>Some Frostlings were trapped and caught by hunters near %s2_city. What do you want to do with them?</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TRAPPED_FROSTLINGS_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TRAPPED_FROSTLINGS_1</Tag>
		<English>Just kill them.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TRAPPED_FROSTLINGS_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TRAPPED_FROSTLINGS_2</Tag>
		<English>Pity those miserable creatures. Release them, they are harmless.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TRAPPED_FROSTLINGS_2_HELP -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TRAPPED_FROSTLINGS_2_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET]May spawn a barbarian Frostling with Weak</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TRAPPED_FROSTLINGS_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TRAPPED_FROSTLINGS_3</Tag>
		<English>Strange creatures! Add them to the freak show, they are amusing!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TRAPPED_FROSTLINGS_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TRAPPED_FROSTLINGS_4</Tag>
		<English>Eat them.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TRAPPED_FROSTLINGS_5 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TRAPPED_FROSTLINGS_5</Tag>
		<English>Hire them, they are our brothers.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<!-- EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION -->
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION</Tag>
		<English>Some people are demonstrating against the endless war in %s2_city.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION_1</Tag>
		<English>And I should care... why?</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION_2</Tag>
		<English>They are right, I will start the negotiations.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION_2_HELP -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION_2_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET]+35 War Weariness</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION_3</Tag>
		<English>Repress them before they spread.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION_3_HELP -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION_3_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET]Every Unit in the City gains 3 XP</English>
		<German>[ICON_BULLET]Jede Einheit in der Stadt erh&#228;lt 3 EP</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION_4</Tag>
		<English>Send them to the front lines. They will learn how to fight.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION_5 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION_5</Tag>
		<English>Hmm... let's have lunch!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION_2_HELP -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PACIFIST_DEMONSTRATION_5_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET]-10 War Weariness[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]All your Vampires gain 3 XP</English>
	</TEXT>
	<!-- EVENT_DEMON_SIGN -->
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEMON_SIGN -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEMON_SIGN</Tag>
		<English>A newborn child in %s2_city has been reported to carry the mark of Agares. What should we do?</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEMON_SIGN_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEMON_SIGN_1</Tag>
		<English>Leave the matter to local officials.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEMON_SIGN_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEMON_SIGN_2</Tag>
		<English>Wondrous! If the king of hope moves upon Erebus, then we shall honor his chosen.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEMON_SIGN_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEMON_SIGN_3</Tag>
		<English>Excellent. If the King of Hope has marked this one, he shall show great service to him. Train him in our temples.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEMON_SIGN_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEMON_SIGN_4</Tag>
		<English>Call the Confessors to remove this mark.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEMON_SIGN_5 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEMON_SIGN_5</Tag>
		<English>This child will be champion among men on the battlefield. Outfit him with the proper equipment and train him to lead our armies.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEMON_SIGN_6 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEMON_SIGN_6</Tag>
		<English>Teach the child he has free will and can forsake his destiny set by the gods.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HANGING_SISTERS -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HANGING_SISTERS</Tag>
		<English>Crazed citizens are celebrating the "Carnival of the Hanging Sisters" in %s2_city. They've raided local graveyards and strung up the dead like puppets!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HANGING_SISTERS_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HANGING_SISTERS_1</Tag>
		<English>Let the carnival begin!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HANGING_SISTERS_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HANGING_SISTERS_2</Tag>
		<English>MAKE IT STOP!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HANGING_SISTERS_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HANGING_SISTERS_3</Tag>
		<English>A great idea!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ASH_COUGH -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ASH_COUGH</Tag>
		<English>People are coughing up ashes and fire in %s2_city. The reason is unknown.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ASH_COUGH_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ASH_COUGH_1</Tag>
		<English>Kill all of the fire breathers, just to be sure.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ASH_COUGH_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ASH_COUGH_2</Tag>
		<English>This is an omen. All hail the dragon!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ASH_COUGH_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ASH_COUGH_3</Tag>
		<English>Purge the evil from our people.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ASH_COUGH_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ASH_COUGH_4</Tag>
		<English>Have our mages investigate this matter.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ASH_COUGH_4_HELP -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ASH_COUGH_4_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET]Who knows what they may find?</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ASH_COUGH_4_OUTCOME_GOOD</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Your adepts were able to harness the flames![COLOR_REVERT]</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ASH_COUGH_4_OUTCOME_NEUTRAL</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_POSITIVE_TEXT]Your adepts were able to stop the cough.[COLOR_REVERT]</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ASH_COUGH_4_OUTCOME_BAD</Tag>
		<English>[COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]The Mage Guild's atempts at healing the fire breathers were unsuccessful, killing many in the process.[COLOR_REVERT]</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEAD_ANGEL -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEAD_ANGEL</Tag>
		<English>An angel's body was found sliced open in the fields. Plants around it are dying off.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEAD_ANGEL_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEAD_ANGEL_1</Tag><English>Sanctify the area.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEAD_ANGEL_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEAD_ANGEL_2</Tag>
		<English>Ensure the angel gets a proper burial.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEAD_ANGEL_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEAD_ANGEL_3</Tag>
		<English>Leave the body to rot.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEAD_ANGEL_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEAD_ANGEL_4</Tag>
		<English>Do our very best to defile the lands further.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEAD_ANGEL_4_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET]Converts the plot to hell terrain</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEAD_ANGEL_5 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEAD_ANGEL_5</Tag>
		<English>Hmm... send our necromancers!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEAD_ANGEL_5_UNIT_NAME</Tag>
		<English>Undead Angel</English>
		<German>Untoter Engel</German>
		<Spanish>&#193;ngel muerto viviente</Spanish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEPRESSED_TOYMAKER -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEPRESSED_TOYMAKER</Tag>
		<English>A depressed toymaker is making tiny coffins for dolls. Their popularity is causing unease among the citizens.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEPRESSED_TOYMAKER_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEPRESSED_TOYMAKER_1</Tag>
		<English>Stop the toymaker, and get these things out of my sight. They make me sick.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEPRESSED_TOYMAKER_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEPRESSED_TOYMAKER_2</Tag>
		<English>I don't care what this toymaker does.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEPRESSED_TOYMAKER_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEPRESSED_TOYMAKER_3</Tag>
		<English>Make tiny Kuriotates dolls to fit these coffins.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEPRESSED_TOYMAKER_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEPRESSED_TOYMAKER_4</Tag>
		<English>They're beautiful! Toymakers should carve these baby coffins in all our cities!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEVASTATING_PLAGUE -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEVASTATING_PLAGUE</Tag>
		<English>A devastating plague has hit %s2_city. Peoples' limbs are rotting black and falling off. Prophets on the streets say it's a sign of the end of times.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEVASTATING_PLAGUE_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEVASTATING_PLAGUE_1</Tag>
		<English>Tell the city doctor's to do everything they can.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEVASTATING_PLAGUE_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEVASTATING_PLAGUE_2</Tag>
		<English>Our people won't suffer for the pointless conflicts of the divine. Send our medics in to stamp out this pandemic.</English>
		<Italian>Our people won't suffer for the pointless conflicts of the divine. Send our medics in to stamp out this pandemic..</Italian>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEVASTATING_PLAGUE_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEVASTATING_PLAGUE_3</Tag>
		<English>Burn the homes of the infected and quarantine the city.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEVASTATING_PLAGUE_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEVASTATING_PLAGUE_4</Tag>
		<English>Bring the corpses here, we'll put them to good use.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_NECRO_CANNIBALISM -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_NECRO_CANNIBALISM</Tag>
		<English>A community in %s2_city has been found to regularily eat their dead!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_NECRO_CANNIBALISM_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_NECRO_CANNIBALISM_1</Tag>
		<English>Put a stop to this!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_NECRO_CANNIBALISM_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_NECRO_CANNIBALISM_2</Tag>
		<English>So what?</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_NECRO_CANNIBALISM_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_NECRO_CANNIBALISM_3</Tag>
		<English>That's the spirit, waste not. Press these resourceful people into military service.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_NECRO_CANNIBALISM_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_NECRO_CANNIBALISM_4</Tag>
		<English>Have the dead fight back. This shall be entertaining.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HELL_PORTAL -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HELL_PORTAL</Tag>
		<English>A portal to Hell has opened in one of your cities.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GHOST_SHIP -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GHOST_SHIP</Tag>
		<English>A mysterious ship has drifted into the harbor of %s2_city. It appears to be in good condition, but it flies the flag of no known nation, and its crew is nowhere to be seen. So far, no one has emerged from the ship, and the townsfolk have not dared to approach it, fearing that it may be cursed.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GHOST_SHIP_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GHOST_SHIP_1</Tag>
		<English>They are superstitious cowards. Order them to board the ship and claim it for our own.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GHOST_SHIP_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GHOST_SHIP_2</Tag>
		<English>They are wise to be prudent. Scuttle the ship, so that whatever curse claimed its crew will not spread to the town.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GHOST_SHIP_1_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GHOST_SHIP_1_1</Tag>
		<English>The rotting remains of the crew emerge from below decks to defend their ship.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GHOST_SHIP_1_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GHOST_SHIP_1_2</Tag>
		<English>The crew are found within the ship, dead of an unknown disease.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GHOST_SHIP_1_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GHOST_SHIP_1_3</Tag>
		<English>A lone crewman is found hiding within the ship, incoherent and violently insane.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GHOST_SHIP_1_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GHOST_SHIP_1_4</Tag>
		<English>The ship is deserted, but holds much valuable cargo.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GHOST_SHIP_1_5 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GHOST_SHIP_1_5</Tag>
		<English>As several townspeople board the ship, it shudders and sinks suddenly into the water, taking them with it.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GHOST_SHIP_1_6 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GHOST_SHIP_1_6</Tag>
		<English>A mysterious map is found in the captain's quarters.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- PROMOTION_ORC_SLAYING -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_PROMOTION_ORC_SLAYING</Tag>
		<English>Orc Slaying</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ORPHANED_GOBLIN -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ORPHANED_GOBLIN</Tag>
		<English>After our troops defeated the goblin horde, a soldier discovered an orphaned Goblin child. Seeing that it posed no threat, he took pity on it and has been taking care of it.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ORPHANED_GOBLIN_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ORPHANED_GOBLIN_1</Tag>
		<English>Punish this weakness by having the soldier kill his new friend, see if the trauma teaches him a lesson.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ORPHANED_GOBLIN_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ORPHANED_GOBLIN_2</Tag>
		<English>Such compassion is noble, allow him to raise the child to follow in his footsteps.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ORPHANED_GOBLIN_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ORPHANED_GOBLIN_3</Tag>
		<English>His actions were noble, but we cannot risk barbarians in our army. Abandon the child.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ORPHANED_GOBLIN_3_HELP -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ORPHANED_GOBLIN_3_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET]May spawn a weak barbarian Goblin nearby.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ORPHANED_GOBLIN_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ORPHANED_GOBLIN_4</Tag>
		<English>The army is no place to raise children! Allow the soldier to return home to raise his new child.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ORPHANED_GOBLIN_4_HELP -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ORPHANED_GOBLIN_4_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET]Receive a Goblin in your capital[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]Your unit loses 1 XP.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_THAT_KIND_OF_DAY -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_THAT_KIND_OF_DAY</Tag>
		<English>The barbarian hordes are at our gates! Our armies have failed us! We are doomed!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PRINCESS_RULE -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PRINCESS_RULE</Tag>
		<English>Your units have spotted a unicorn outside of %s2_city.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PRINCESS_RULE_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PRINCESS_RULE_1</Tag>
		<English>Kill it, the horn alone is worth a fortune!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PRINCESS_RULE_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PRINCESS_RULE_2</Tag>
		<English>Kill it, it's horn can purify water.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PRINCESS_RULE_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PRINCESS_RULE_3</Tag>
		<English>Dinnertime, boys!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PRINCESS_RULE_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PRINCESS_RULE_4</Tag>
		<English>Don't kill it!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PRINCESS_RULE_4_MESSAGE -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PRINCESS_RULE_4_MESSAGE</Tag>
		<English>A few days later, a scouting party encounters the unicorn again. Or at least, the parts of it that haven't been picked clean by scavengers already. Judging by the amount of bite- and claw-marks on the corpse, it would appear that this innocent creature was ill-suited for the wildlands of Erebus.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_CORRUPT_JUDGE -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_CORRUPT_JUDGE</Tag>
		<English>A new judge has been very effective at keeping the streets safe in %s2_city, but we have found evidence that proves beyond a shadow of a doubt that he is corrupt.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_CORRUPT_JUDGE_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_CORRUPT_JUDGE_1</Tag>
		<English>As long as the populace sleeps safely at night, I do not care if he skims a little off the top.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_CORRUPT_JUDGE_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_CORRUPT_JUDGE_2</Tag>
		<English>Close the courthouse and see that it that he is brought to account for his crimes.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_CORRUPT_JUDGE_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_CORRUPT_JUDGE_3</Tag>
		<English>I will not stand for this. Make a full example of him and send a priest of Order to serve in his place.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_CORRUPT_JUDGE_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_CORRUPT_JUDGE_4</Tag>
		<English>He is obvious not being subtle enough. Show him how to hide his tracks... and see to it that we receive our cut.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_WAYWARD_ELVES -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_WAYWARD_ELVES</Tag>
		<English>We have come across an isolated village of elves that managed to survive during the harsh Age of Ice. What do you want us to do with them?</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_WAYWARD_ELVES_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_WAYWARD_ELVES_1</Tag>
		<English>What do I care? Leave them to their fate.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_WAYWARD_ELVES_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_WAYWARD_ELVES_2</Tag>
		<English>Welcome them home!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_WAYWARD_ELVES_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_WAYWARD_ELVES_3</Tag>
		<English>Wipe them out to let our troops have some combat training.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_WAYWARD_ELVES_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_WAYWARD_ELVES_4</Tag>
		<English>Wonderful! More petlings!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_WAYWARD_ELVES_5 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_WAYWARD_ELVES_5</Tag>
		<English>Offer them refuge in our nearest town.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_RENOWNED_MARKET -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_RENOWNED_MARKET</Tag>
		<English>The market in %s2_city is drawing widespread attention as a place one can go to buy anything their heart desires.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_RENOWNED_MARKET_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_RENOWNED_MARKET_1</Tag>
		<English>Make a personal visit to the market to give my endorsement.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_RENOWNED_MARKET_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_RENOWNED_MARKET_2</Tag>
		<English>Send out word with the traders! Our market will be known world-wide.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_RENOWNED_MARKET_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_RENOWNED_MARKET_3</Tag>
		<English>Have our sages search the bazaar for interesting relics of the past.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_BOARD_GAME -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_BOARD_GAME</Tag>
		<English>Sire, our sages in %s2_city have created a strategic board game based on Erebus' history. They call it "Fall From Heaven".</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_BOARD_GAME_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_BOARD_GAME_1</Tag>
		<English>Bah, those sages have too much time on their hands.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_BOARD_GAME_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_BOARD_GAME_2</Tag>
		<English>It could become a widespread pastime. Sponsor the game!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_BOARD_GAME_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_BOARD_GAME_3</Tag>
		<English>Have the sages come up with a fantasy variant. Call it "Civilization".</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_BOARD_GAME_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_BOARD_GAME_4</Tag>
		<English>Wait, Fall from Heaven? Blasphemy!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TRAVELLER -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TRAVELLER</Tag>
		<English>An experienced traveler has just arrived at your palace. For a little fee he can tell one story. What would you like to hear about?</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TRAVELLER_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TRAVELLER_1</Tag>
		<English>Tell me about natural wonders of Erebus.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TRAVELLER_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TRAVELLER_2</Tag>
		<English>Tell me about remnants from ancient Ages.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TRAVELLER_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TRAVELLER_3</Tag>
		<English>Tell me about holy shrines of the gods.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TRAVELLER_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TRAVELLER_4</Tag>
		<English>Tell me about places related to the angels.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TRAVELLER_5 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TRAVELLER_5</Tag>
		<English>Tell me about the biggest city you have ever seen.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TRAVELLER_6 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TRAVELLER_6</Tag>
		<English>I have neither time nor money for this.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_UNFORTUNATE_ASSASSIN -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_UNFORTUNATE_ASSASSIN</Tag>
		<English>There's just been an assassination attempt on you! What do you want to do with the assassin?</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_UNFORTUNATE_ASSASSIN_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_UNFORTUNATE_ASSASSIN_1</Tag>
		<English>Don't we have a feast scheduled for tomorrow?</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_UNFORTUNATE_ASSASSIN_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_UNFORTUNATE_ASSASSIN_2</Tag>
		<English>Stop asking stupid questions and execute her!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_UNFORTUNATE_ASSASSIN_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_UNFORTUNATE_ASSASSIN_3</Tag>
		<English>Throw her into jail, and make sure she is properly guarded.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_UNFORTUNATE_ASSASSIN_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_UNFORTUNATE_ASSASSIN_4</Tag>
		<English>Let her go. I shall not fight violence with more violence.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_UNFORTUNATE_ASSASSIN_5 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_UNFORTUNATE_ASSASSIN_5</Tag>
		<English>She managed to sneak past my guards? We need people with such potential. Make her an offer she can't refuse.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_UNFORTUNATE_ASSASSIN_4_CONT -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_UNFORTUNATE_ASSASSIN_4_CONT</Tag>
		<English>A stranger asks for an audience.[NEWLINE][TAB]"I was once hired to kill you, but I failed and you forgave me. I've seen much of the world and I learned that mercy is the only thing that can save erebus. Please accept me in your service."</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_UNFORTUNATE_ASSASSIN_4_CONT_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_UNFORTUNATE_ASSASSIN_4_CONT_1</Tag>
		<English>I'm glad you finally understand.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_OVERCROWDED_DUNGEON -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_OVERCROWDED_DUNGEON</Tag>
		<English>Our dungeon in %s2_city is so full of criminals that there is barely enough room for all inmates. Escapes, fights and assaults on guards are all reported.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_OVERCROWDED_DUNGEON_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_OVERCROWDED_DUNGEON_1</Tag>
		<English>Who cares? A dungeon is not supposed to be a comfortable inn.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_OVERCROWDED_DUNGEON_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_OVERCROWDED_DUNGEON_2</Tag>
		<English>Hire more guards and expand the dungeons prisoner capacity.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_OVERCROWDED_DUNGEON_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_OVERCROWDED_DUNGEON_3</Tag>
		<English>Release all small-time crooks, so there is enough room for true criminals and thugs.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_OVERCROWDED_DUNGEON_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_OVERCROWDED_DUNGEON_4</Tag>
		<English>Make a full effort to reduce a crime rate in the city and teach criminals how to do useful labor.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_OVERCROWDED_DUNGEON_5 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_OVERCROWDED_DUNGEON_5</Tag>
		<English>Execute the entire dungeon, every last one of them, they are all scum anyway. That will make some space.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL</Tag>
		<English>Some locals in your empire have discovered that the nearby mound is actually an ancient burial site for some forgotten warrior! They are fearful of the consequences of disturbing the grave.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_1</Tag>
		<English>Let the warrior's bones rest in peace.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_2</Tag>
		<English>An ancient warrior, this must be one of our ancestors lost to history! Set up a memorial in their honor.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_2_HELP -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_2_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET]20% chance:[NEWLINE][TAB][ICON_BULLET]A Skeleton Warrior with Heroic Defense appears</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_3</Tag>
		<English>Interesting... let's seal the grave and set up a tourist attraction. Just to ease the villagers fears, of course.</English>
		<Spanish>Interesting... lets seal the grave and set up a tourist attraction. Just to ease the villagers fears, of course.</Spanish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_3_HELP -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_3_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET]90% chance:[NEWLINE][TAB][ICON_BULLET]A Skeleton Warrior with Heroic Defense appears</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_4</Tag>
		<English>This warrior was buried before the Age of Ice, let's profit from their death. Loot the grave!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_4_HELP -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_4_HELP</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET]60% chance:[NEWLINE][TAB][ICON_BULLET]+90 Gold[NEWLINE][ICON_BULLET]40% chance:[NEWLINE][TAB][ICON_BULLET]A Skeleton Warrior with Heroic Defense appears</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_4_JEWELRY -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_4_JEWELRY</Tag>
		<English>The grave is full of ancient jewelry</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_X_WARRIOR_RISES -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ANCIENT_BURIAL_X_WARRIOR_RISES</Tag>
		<English>The ancient warrior rises to defend his grave</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_MAD_GOLEMICIST -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_MAD_GOLEMICIST</Tag>
		<English>While on patrol, your unit stumbles across the laboratory of an isolated golem-maker. As the golem-maker greets you, you see a strange, crazed glint in his eye. Some of the half-finished golems that you can see lying around appear disturbingly...biological. "Welcome," the golem-maker says. "I could use another deft pair of hands for my experiments. My golem assistants are strong, but they lack manual dexterity. Will you help me?"</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_MAD_GOLEMICIST_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_MAD_GOLEMICIST_1</Tag>
		<English>No, this place makes me nervous. I'm going to leave now.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_MAD_GOLEMICIST_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_MAD_GOLEMICIST_2</Tag>
		<English>These experiments are an abomination! Kill him, and seize his gold and his magical materials. But watch out for his golems!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_MAD_GOLEMICIST_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_MAD_GOLEMICIST_3</Tag>
		<English>Yes, I will help you.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_MAD_GOLEMICIST_3_BARNAXUS -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_MAD_GOLEMICIST_3_BARNAXUS</Tag>
		<English>"Oh my, what a perfect specimen! I can't see how I could possibly improve you, my friend. Maybe if I remove this piece...oh no! I broke it!"</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_MAD_GOLEMICIST_3_GOLEM -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_MAD_GOLEMICIST_3_GOLEM</Tag>
		<English>"Ah yes, I can see much room for improvement here. Let me just adjust this and tweak that...there!"</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_MAD_GOLEMICIST_3_HUMAN_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_MAD_GOLEMICIST_3_HUMAN_1</Tag>
		<English>"If you'll just hold this intestine while I cast the enchantment .... There we go! It's perfect!"</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_MAD_GOLEMICIST_3_HUMAN_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_MAD_GOLEMICIST_3_HUMAN_2</Tag>
		<English>"Just hold this piece for me...no! What are you doing? You dropped it! My experiment is ruined! Now I will need new experimental materials. Golems, seize them! Hold them down while I saw open the skulls. It's a tight space in there, but I have some excellent clockwork that will fit once I remove the useless gray matter."</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_YOUNGER_COUNCIL -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_YOUNGER_COUNCIL</Tag>
		<English>Younger adults from %s2_city are complaining about the local Elder Council. They claim that its members spend their time telling stories from their youth instead of doing anything useful. They demand representation in the council so that they can direct its work.</English>
		<French>Younger adults from %s2_city are complaining about the local Elder Council. They claim that its members spend their time telling stories from their youth instead of doing anything useful. They demand representation in the council so that they could direct its work.</French>
		<German>Younger adults from %s2_city are complaining about the local Elder Council. They claim that its members spend their time telling stories from their youth instead of doing anything useful. They demand representation in the council so that they could direct its work.</German>
		<Italian>Younger adults from %s2_city are complaining about the local Elder Council. They claim that its members spend their time telling stories from their youth instead of doing anything useful. They demand representation in the council so that they could direct its work.</Italian>
		<Spanish>Younger adults from %s2_city are complaining about the local Elder Council. They claim that its members spend their time telling stories from their youth instead of doing anything useful. They demand representation in the council so that they could direct its work.</Spanish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_YOUNGER_COUNCIL_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_YOUNGER_COUNCIL_1</Tag>
		<English>There is a reason why it's called an Elder Council. We shall keep the tradition.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_YOUNGER_COUNCIL_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_YOUNGER_COUNCIL_2</Tag>
		<English>Let some responsible younger citizens join the council.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_YOUNGER_COUNCIL_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_YOUNGER_COUNCIL_3</Tag>
		<English>Get rid of the elders. They have no idea how today's world works.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_YOUNGER_COUNCIL_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_YOUNGER_COUNCIL_4</Tag>
		<English>The state should take care that the elders do their job. Assign some official to the council.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_COOKBOOK -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_COOKBOOK</Tag>
		<English>An ancient cookbook from the Age of Magic has been discovered in the library of %s2_city.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_COOKBOOK_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_COOKBOOK_1</Tag>
		<English>That's great news - I have always wanted to know what people from that lost age ate.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_COOKBOOK_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_COOKBOOK_2</Tag>
		<English>That can not be a good omen. This book must be cursed. Have it burned.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ELDER_DEATH -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ELDER_DEATH</Tag>
		<English>A member of the Elder Council in %s2_city recently died. He was an respected member, how shall we honor his death?</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ELDER_DEATH_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ELDER_DEATH_1</Tag>
		<English>Why are you bothering me with this?</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ELDER_DEATH_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ELDER_DEATH_2</Tag>
		<English>We will fund a lavish funeral in celebration of the man's life.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ELDER_DEATH_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ELDER_DEATH_3</Tag>
		<English>He can serve me in the afterlife.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ELDER_DEATH_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ELDER_DEATH_4</Tag>
		<English>Search the city for a new member for the Elder Council.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_SKILLED_JEWELER -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SKILLED_JEWELER</Tag>
		<English>A very promising journeyman in %s2_city is infuriating local master craftsman by wasting his time on making jewelry instead of weapons and tools.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_SKILLED_JEWELER_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SKILLED_JEWELER_1</Tag>
		<English>We could use a service of a skilled jeweler. Fund him his own workshop.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_SKILLED_JEWELER_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SKILLED_JEWELER_2</Tag>
		<English>He should return to his work as a blacksmith.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_SKILLED_JEWELER_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SKILLED_JEWELER_3</Tag>
		<English>Let him do both by creating and then decorating high quality weapons with jewels and inlays to increase their value for the glory of Kilmorph.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GREAT_SPEAKER -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GREAT_SPEAKER</Tag>
		<English>One of the lawyers in %s2_city is gaining renown for his eloquent, moving and honest speeches. People say he raises the use of language to the rank of art.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_GREAT_SPEAKER_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_GREAT_SPEAKER_1</Tag>
		<English>I suppose that's good news as long as he does not use his talent against us.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_REDECORATION -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_REDECORATION</Tag>
		<English>Our chief architect suggests adding new decorations to the palace.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_REDECORATION_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_REDECORATION_1</Tag>
		<English>We could add some stone statues.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_REDECORATION_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_REDECORATION_2</Tag>
		<English>How about some marble sculptures.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_REDECORATION_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_REDECORATION_3</Tag>
		<English>Maybe some golden ornaments here and there would do the trick.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_REDECORATION_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_REDECORATION_4</Tag>
		<English>I think bronze statues would do just fine.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_REDECORATION_5 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_REDECORATION_5</Tag>
		<English>I'm afraid we can not afford this.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_NO_TEXT -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_NO_TEXT</Tag>
		<English></English>
		<French></French>
		<German></German>
		<Italian></Italian>
		<Spanish></Spanish>
	</TEXT>
<!-- MORE EVENTS MOD ENDS -->
<!-- MORE EVENTS MOD EXPANDED STARTS -->
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_URANIUM -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_URANIUM</Tag>
		<English>Miners near the city of %s2_city have found a strange new mineral all over the mine. They call it Uranium, and it glows slightly in the dark. Unfortunately it is slowly poisoning them and their tools. What shall we do?</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_URANIUM_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_URANIUM_1</Tag>
		<English>Our Earth adepts should be able to find a way to use this Uranium safely.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_URANIUM_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_URANIUM_2</Tag>
		<English>Station a Life adept at the mine to keep the miners healthy.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_URANIUM_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_URANIUM_3</Tag>
		<English>Safety first - take the necessary precautions to protect our miners.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_URANIUM_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_URANIUM_4</Tag>
		<English>Keep it quiet, but KEEP them working.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_OIL -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_OIL</Tag>
		<English>A desert area floodplain near the city of %s2_city has a thick, black, stinking, oily liquid welling up from the ground in many places. It is reducing available farmland.</English>
		<Italian>A desert area floodplain near the city of %s2_city has a thick, black, stinking, oily liquid welling up from the ground in many places. It is reducing available farmland. </Italian>
		<Spanish>A desert area floodplain near the city of %s2_city has a thick, black, stinking, oily liquid welling up from the ground in many places. It is reducing available farmland. </Spanish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_OIL_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_OIL_1</Tag>
		<English>We'll never find a use for this worthless "oil".</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_OIL_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_OIL_2</Tag>
		<English>I wonder if this "oil" burns?</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_OIL_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_OIL_3</Tag>
		<English>Hmmm, this "oil" may help us lubricate our machinery better.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_WINDS_FROM_HELL -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_WINDS_FROM_HELL</Tag>
		<English>Massive storms are slowly destroying our windmills near the city of %s2_city. Eyewitnesses say the winds sound like they come from the very Vaults of Hell. What can we do?</English>
		<Spanish>Massive storms are slowly destroying our windmills near the city of %s2_city. Eyewitnesses say the winds sound like they come from the very Vaults of Hell. What can we do? </Spanish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_WINDS_FROM_HELL_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_WINDS_FROM_HELL_1</Tag>
		<English>Our Air adepts can redirect the winds until the storms subside.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_WINDS_FROM_HELL_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_WINDS_FROM_HELL_2</Tag>
		<English>Sacrifice a soul to appease these winds.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_WINDS_FROM_HELL_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_WINDS_FROM_HELL_3</Tag>
		<English>What can we do? Let the storms run their course and rebuild.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TREANT_RAGE -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TREANT_RAGE</Tag>
		<English>Logging operations in the forests near the city of %s2_city are in danger. Treants are enraged at tree cuttings and their attacks have caught us by surprise. Loggers are fleeing and buildings being destroyed.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TREANT_RAGE_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TREANT_RAGE_1</Tag>
		<English>Quick, our Nature adepts should be able to calm them down.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TREANT_RAGE_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TREANT_RAGE_2</Tag>
		<English>Rush our priests there to convince the treants we replant as well as cut.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_TREANT_RAGE_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_TREANT_RAGE_3</Tag>
		<English>Our troops cannot reach there in time. We shall just have to rebuild our lumbermills.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- NEWS_EVENT_TREANT_RAGE_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_NEWS_EVENT_TREANT_RAGE_3</Tag>
		<English>Treants enraged by tree cuttings have attacked the %s1_civ_adjective logging operations.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PERFECT_STORM -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PERFECT_STORM</Tag>
		<English>An unexpectedly fierce storm has struck land near the city of %s2_city, devastating our coastal waters.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PERFECT_STORM_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PERFECT_STORM_1</Tag>
		<English>A disaster. We shall have to repair or rebuild almost everything there.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PERFECT_STORM_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PERFECT_STORM_2</Tag>
		<English>A disaster. We shall have to rebuild our pirate cove.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- NEWS_EVENT_PERFECT_STORM_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_NEWS_EVENT_PERFECT_STORM_1</Tag>
		<English>An uxpectedly fierce storm has devastated %s1_civ_adjective fishing operations.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PEAT -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PEAT</Tag>
		<English>The swamps near the city of %s2_city have an abundant supply of peat.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_PEAT_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_PEAT_1</Tag>
		<English>That's good news.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_BREAD -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_BREAD</Tag>
		<English>Millers using the windmills near the city of %s2_city have discovered a more efficient way to make bread flour with less waste.</English>
		<Italian>Millers using the windmills near the city of %s2_city have discovered a more efficient way to make bread flour with less waste. </Italian>
		<Spanish>Millers using the windmills near the city of %s2_city have discovered a more efficient way to make bread flour with less waste. </Spanish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_BREAD_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_BREAD_1</Tag>
		<English>Now all we need is the jug of wine and thou, as the poet once said.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_SUTTERS_MILL -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SUTTERS_MILL</Tag>
		<English>Small amounts of silver have been discovered near the workshops of the city of %s2_city. The workshops are using it to increase the value of their products.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_SUTTERS_MILL_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SUTTERS_MILL_1</Tag>
		<English>Good, but don't let it start a silver rush.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_FROG_LEGS -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_FROG_LEGS</Tag>
		<English>The swamps near the city of %s2_city have a plethora of large edible frogs. Their legs have become a delicacy.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_FROG_LEGS_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_FROG_LEGS_1</Tag>
		<English>They do taste like chicken, don't they?</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- NEWS_EVENT_FROG_LEGS_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_NEWS_EVENT_FROG_LEGS_1</Tag>
		<English>Frog legs have become a delicacy in %s1_civ_adjective lands.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_THREAD_NECROMANCY -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_THREAD_NECROMANCY</Tag>
		<English>An issue long thought decided is being discussed again amongst our people - risen from the dead, so to speak. Heated arguments are breaking out daily, dividing family and friends.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_THREAD_NECROMANCY_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_THREAD_NECROMANCY_1</Tag>
		<English>Our stability is more important than those raising this issue. So let's have lunch.</English>
		<Spanish>Our stability is more important than those raising this issue. So let's have lunch. </Spanish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_THREAD_NECROMANCY_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_THREAD_NECROMANCY_2</Tag>
		<English>I have an idea for a series of public ice sculptures using those causing this unrest.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_THREAD_NECROMANCY_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_THREAD_NECROMANCY_3</Tag>
		<English>Let's show the people real necromancy and stop this irritation.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_THREAD_NECROMANCY_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_THREAD_NECROMANCY_4</Tag>
		<English>It's hard to talk and spread dissension when your lungs are filled with water.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_THREAD_NECROMANCY_5 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_THREAD_NECROMANCY_5</Tag>
		<English>Dissent of such a random nature is a threat to our society and will not be tolerated. Crackdown on this and train our priests better to avoid this happening ever again.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_THREAD_NECROMANCY_6 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_THREAD_NECROMANCY_6</Tag>
		<English>Just let it be - maybe it will die away again.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_POISONED_WATER -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_POISONED_WATER</Tag>
		<English>The water supplies for our city of %s2_city have somehow became tainted - possibly they were poisoned by one of our enemies. Water shortages are widespread.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_POISONED_WATER_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_POISONED_WATER_1</Tag>
		<English>Have our Water adepts purify our water supplies.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_POISONED_WATER_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_POISONED_WATER_2</Tag>
		<English>The powers of Aquae Sucellus will have already removed any and all poisons.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_POISONED_WATER_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_POISONED_WATER_3</Tag>
		<English>Begin cleansing operations immediately, and ration our water supplies until done.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_POISONED_WATER_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_POISONED_WATER_4</Tag>
		<English>Begin rationing our water supplies until nature herself finally cleans them.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_POISONED_WATER_CONT_5 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_POISONED_WATER_CONT_5</Tag>
		<English>The water supplies for our city of %s2_city have finally become pure again.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_POISONED_WATER_CONT_6 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_POISONED_WATER_CONT_6</Tag>
		<English>The water supplies for our city of %s2_city have finally become pure again.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- NEWS_EVENT_POISONED_WATER_CONT_5 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_NEWS_EVENT_POISONED_WATER_CONT_5</Tag>
		<English>The water supplies for our city of %s2_city have finally become pure again.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- NEWS_EVENT_POISONED_WATER_CONT_6 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_NEWS_EVENT_POISONED_WATER_CONT_6</Tag>
		<English>The water supplies for our city of %s2_city have finally become pure again.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_POISONED_WATER_HELP_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_POISONED_WATER_HELP_3</Tag>
		<English>This city (only) has a -2 health penalty for 5 turns.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_POISONED_WATER_HELP_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_POISONED_WATER_HELP_4</Tag>
		<English>This city (only) has a -3 health penalty and -1 anger for 10 turns.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_FRAMED -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_FRAMED</Tag>
		<English>The %s1_civ_adjective Empire has had a scandal break out that somehow it looks like our diplomats there were involved in. Our relations with them will suffer unless we can prove we're innocent. We are, right?</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_FRAMED_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_FRAMED_1</Tag>
		<English>Our Mind adepts will prove we are innocent.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_FRAMED_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_FRAMED_2</Tag>
		<English>We shall prove another civilization caused this.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_FRAMED_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_FRAMED_3</Tag>
		<English>We are innocent, but have no proof.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_FRAMED_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_FRAMED_4</Tag>
		<English>Yes, we're innocent. But tell them we did it - and that they deserved it.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_FRAMED_OTHER_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_FRAMED_OTHER_1</Tag>
		<English>The %s1_civ_adjective ambassador has been implicated in a scandal involving important people in our government. This has adversely affected our relations with their country.</English>
		<French>The %s1_civ_adjective ambassador has been implicated in a scandal involving important people in our government. This has adversely affected our relations with their country. </French>
		<Spanish>The %s1_civ_adjective ambassador has been implicated in a scandal involving important people in our government. This has adversely affected our relations with their country. </Spanish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEMONIC_TOWER -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEMONIC_TOWER</Tag>
		<English>A group of cultists in an Ancient Tower have summoned a Demon from Hell. Fortunately a band of adventurers killed the cultists and trapped the demon in the Tower.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEMONIC_TOWER_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEMONIC_TOWER_1</Tag>
		<English>Let no one enter the Ancient Tower until we can kill or banish it.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_DEMONIC_TOWER_HELP_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_DEMONIC_TOWER_HELP_1</Tag>
		<English>A weakened and immobile demon appears in the tower.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ANCIENT_TOWER_LORE -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ANCIENT_TOWER_LORE</Tag>
		<English>We have discovered a cache of pre-Age of Ice books in an Ancient Tower. The books are decorated with gold and jewels, but fragile - reading them may end up destroying them. And they may be dangerous to read. What shall we do?</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ANCIENT_TOWER_LORE_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ANCIENT_TOWER_LORE_1</Tag>
		<English>Have them sent - carefully - to our scholars for study.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ANCIENT_TOWER_LORE_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ANCIENT_TOWER_LORE_2</Tag>
		<English>Have them sent - carefully - to our priests and mystics for study.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_ANCIENT_TOWER_LORE_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_ANCIENT_TOWER_LORE_3</Tag>
		<English>Keep the gold and jewels, but burn the books just to be safe.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_STORMY_SEAS -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_STORMY_SEAS</Tag>
		<English>A sudden storm caught a number of our %s3_unit by surprise. They were all sunk or damaged beyond repair.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_STORMY_SEAS_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_STORMY_SEAS_1</Tag>
		<English>As it is said, anyone can steer a ship when the sea is calm.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_RALPH_AND_SAM -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_RALPH_AND_SAM</Tag>
		<English>Packs of wolves near the city of %s2_city have fed well on the local sheep flocks and grown very large and aggressive.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_RALPH_AND_SAM_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_RALPH_AND_SAM_1</Tag>
		<English>Those who cried wolf were telling the truth this time, I see.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_RALPH_AND_SAM_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_RALPH_AND_SAM_2</Tag>
		<English>Kill the pack leaders - then they shall be our pack of wolves.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_RALPH_AND_SAM_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_RALPH_AND_SAM_3</Tag>
		<English>Hire some adventurers to deal with them.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_RALPH_AND_SAM_HELP_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_RALPH_AND_SAM_HELP_1</Tag>
		<English>An immobile barbarian Wolf Pack appears.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_LANUN_PIRATES -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_LANUN_PIRATES</Tag>
		<English>Ships of the Lanun have arrived in our waters, seeking gold and plunder!</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_LANUN_PIRATES_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_LANUN_PIRATES_1</Tag>
		<English>We must marshal our fleets to defeat these Lanun raiders.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_WORLD_LANUN_PIRATES -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_WORLD_LANUN_PIRATES</Tag>
		<English>Ships of the %s1_civ_adjective Empire have come under attack from [COLOR_NEGATIVE_TEXT]Lanun Raiders[COLOR_REVERT]!</English>
		<French>Les bateaux de l'empire de %s1_civ_adjective ont relev&#233; de l'attaque des corsaires!</French>
		<German>Schiffe des %s1_civ_adjective Reiches sind unter Angriff von den Seer&#228;ubern gekommen!</German>
		<Italian>Le navi dell'impero di %s1_civ_adjective sono rientrato nell'attacco dai corsairs!</Italian>
		<Spanish>&#161;Las naves del imperio de %s1_civ_adjective han venido bajo ataque de los corsairs!</Spanish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_LANUN_PIRATES_HELP_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_LANUN_PIRATES_HELP_1</Tag>
		<English>[ICON_BULLET]A dangerous number of so-called [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Lanun Privateer[COLOR_REVERT] units have gathered near our waters.</English>
		<French>[ICON_BULLET]Un nombre dangereux des [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Privateer[COLOR_REVERT] barbares est apparu de notre eaux.</French>
		<German>[ICON_BULLET]Eine gef&#228;hrliche Anzahl von barbarischen [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Privateer[COLOR_REVERT] haben nahe unserem Wasser gelaicht.</German>
		<Italian>[ICON_BULLET]Ai nostri confini c'&#232; un pericoloso numero di [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Privateer[COLOR_REVERT] barbari.</Italian>
		<Spanish>[ICON_BULLET]Un n&#250;mero peligroso de unidades b&#225;rbaras de la [COLOR_UNIT_TEXT]Privateer[COLOR_REVERT] ha frezado cerca de nuestras aguas.</Spanish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_CENTAUR_TRIBE -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_CENTAUR_TRIBE</Tag>
		<English>A tribe of centaurs has claimed the local herds of horses and the land they graze on for their tribe solely. The centaurs ask only to be left alone.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_CENTAUR_TRIBE_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_CENTAUR_TRIBE_1</Tag>
		<English>No, we claim that land.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_CENTAUR_TRIBE_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_CENTAUR_TRIBE_2</Tag>
		<English>We will gladly let them manage the land there. In return we offer them protection and a place in our civilization.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_CENTAUR_TRIBE_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_CENTAUR_TRIBE_3</Tag>
		<English>We welcome all who seek help not from heaven but from themselves, and offer them our friendship.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_CENTAUR_TRIBE_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_CENTAUR_TRIBE_4</Tag>
		<English>If they will manage the herds for us, we will extend them our protection.</English>
		<Spanish>If they will manage the herds for us, we will extend them our protection. </Spanish>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_CENTAUR_TRIBE_HELP_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_CENTAUR_TRIBE_HELP_1</Tag>
		<English>An immobile barbarian Centaur Archer appears.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_SEASERPENT -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SEASERPENT</Tag>
		<English>The sea life is so bountiful off our coasts that a pod of sea serpents has made one of our most productive fishing areas their personal larder.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_SEASERPENT_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SEASERPENT_1</Tag>
		<English>We will have to send our navy to deal with them.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_SEASERPENT_HELP_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SEASERPENT_HELP_1</Tag>
		<English>An immobile Sea Serpent appears on the plot.</English>
	</TEXT>
    <TEXT><!-- EVENT_MONKEY_SEE -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_MONKEY_SEE</Tag>
		<English>A motley collection of monkeys, apes, and gorillas has descended upon our banana crops, eating everything in sight.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_MONKEY_SEE_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_MONKEY_SEE_1</Tag>
		<English>Monkey see, monkey do, as the old saying goes.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_MONKEY_SEE_HELP_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_MONKEY_SEE_HELP_1</Tag>
		<English>A Gorilla appears on the plot.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_KURIOTATES_FISH -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_KURIOTATES_FISH</Tag>
		<English>The citizens of our settlement of %s2_city have constructed a small fishing fleet themselves to catch their plentiful fish.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_KURIOTATES_CLAM -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_KURIOTATES_CLAM</Tag>
		<English>The citizens of our settlement of %s2_city have constructed a small fishing fleet themselves to harvest their bountiful clam beds.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_KURIOTATES_CRAB -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_KURIOTATES_CRAB</Tag>
		<English>The citizens of our settlement of %s2_city have constructed a small fishing fleet themselves to harvest their abundant crabs.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_KURIOTATES_SHRIMP -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_KURIOTATES_SHRIMP</Tag>
		<English>The citizens of our settlement of %s2_city have constructed a small fishing fleet themselves to harvest their copious schools of shrimps.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_KURIOTATES_FISH_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_KURIOTATES_FISH_1</Tag>
		<English>That is the type of citizen initiative I like to hear about.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_KURIOTATES_CLAM_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_KURIOTATES_CLAM_1</Tag>
		<English>That is the type of citizen initiative I like to hear about.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_KURIOTATES_CRAB_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_KURIOTATES_CRAB_1</Tag>
		<English>That is the type of citizen initiative I like to hear about.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_KURIOTATES_SHRIMP_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_KURIOTATES_SHRIMP_1</Tag>
		<English>That is the type of citizen initiative I like to hear about.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HAUNTED_CASTLE -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HAUNTED_CASTLE</Tag>
		<English>Workers expanding the dungeons of a %s8_improvement near the city of %s2_city have disturbed the mass grave of a pre-Age of Ice battleground. They have fled in terror, saying the vengeful dead are rising.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HAUNTED_CASTLE_1 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HAUNTED_CASTLE_1</Tag>
		<English>If the dead are rising then they can rise into our armies.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HAUNTED_CASTLE_2 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HAUNTED_CASTLE_2</Tag>
		<English>Send some well-guarded Spirit adepts there and have them calm the restless spirits for good.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HAUNTED_CASTLE_3 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HAUNTED_CASTLE_3</Tag>
		<English>Send some well-guarded Life adepts there and have them Sanctify the ancient mass grave.</English>
	</TEXT>	
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HAUNTED_CASTLE_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HAUNTED_CASTLE_4</Tag>
		<English>Keep everyone out of there until we destroy those risen spirits.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT><!-- EVENT_HAUNTED_CASTLE_HELP_4 -->
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_HAUNTED_CASTLE_HELP_4</Tag>
		<English>An immobile barbarian Spectre appears.</English>
	</TEXT>
<!-- EXPANDED EVENTS END -->
<!-- From Magister Modmod START -->
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SICKNESS_3</Tag>
		<English>We should use this disease to our advantage against our mortal enemies.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SIGN_AERON_1</Tag>
		<English>The Lord of Murder has chosen us to be his children. Let us rejoice in the power he grants us over the weak.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SIGN_ARAWN</Tag>
		<English>Astrologers report that the Shroud has moved into prominence. This constellation is sacred to Arawn and it is said to be a good time to visit gravesites and remember those that have passed on. Although The God of Death himself does nothing to honor this alignment, his archangel Gyra works to make sure that the dead may rest in peace.</English>
		<German>Eure Sterndeuter berichten, dass das Leichentuch den Nachthimmel beherrscht. Dieses Sternbild ist Arawn geweiht und es heißt, dass dies eine gute Zeit sei, um Grabstätten zu besuchen und den Verblichenen zu gedenken. Although The God of Death himself does nothing to honor this alignment, his archangel Gyra works to make sure that the dead may rest in peace.</German>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SIGN_ARAWN_1</Tag>
		<English>Let us honor the Lord of the Otherworld, though he cares not what we do in this life.</English>
	</TEXT>
	<TEXT>
		<Tag>TXT_KEY_EVENT_SIGN_BHALL_1</Tag>
		<English>Bring forth the sacrifices! Let the Bhall-Orcs fuel the Sacred Flame with the blood of our enemies, and ignite us with the passion of our mistress!</English>
	</TEXT>
</Civ4GameText>
